<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<textData 
	scrollColor="0x006699"
	trackColor="0x111111"
	bgdColor="0x000000">

<header><![CDATA[<font color = "#ffffff" size ="45">Etireno</font>]]></header>
<text><![CDATA[<img src="images/misc/Etireno Project P1 copy.jpg" width="200" height="133"/>"On April 17th 2001 the Etireno Slave ship limped into a Benin port at 02:00 only 23 children were removed from the ship, it was reported that as many as 250 children boarded the Etireno weeks earlier - the majority of the children were all aged between 10 and 14 years old" <b>- FACT -</b>

"Across the world approximately 800,000 children are trafficked and enslaved every year" <b>- FACT -</b>

"Approximately 75% of all children who get repatriated our diagnosed with HIV" <b>- FACT -</b>

"Etireno" is a feature film that is based on true events that follow the paths of the slave traders and their captives as they scheme their way across Benin with the Red Cross hot on their heals. Bringing in elements from The Royal Navy and following the British Diplomats as they attempt to intervene using powers granted to them from the UN this story is a heart wrenching story of humanity and survival.

This feature has been developed as a charity feature film in conjunction with Antislavery International and its sole purpose is to raise the much-needed funds to educate and eradicate slavery from around the world.
  
<b>Interested cast are:</b>
Morgan Freeman: 	Fig - "Slave trader" (Interested)
Vanessa Redgrave: 	Dianne Williams - "Red Cross Boss"  (Interested)
John Hurt: 		Sir Fredrick Pyne – British Diplomat"  (Interested)

<b>Suggested cast are:</b>
Natalie Portman: Rachel Middleton - "Red Cross worker"
Djimon Hounsou: Elimu - "Red Cross worker' 
Domonic Cooper: James Cardwell - "Freelance Photo Journalist"
Hugh Bonneville: Captain Harvey-Middleton - "British Navy Captain"
Don Warrington: Eze Mogorro - "Slave Boss"
Michael Kenneth Williams: Panga - "Slave trader"
Nick Nolte: Stefan Kruger -  "South African slave trader"
Frankie Faison: Etireno ship's captain

Filming to take place probably in England / Morocco / Australia or Caribbean
<img src="images/misc/Boy in the wire.jpg" width="300" height="250"/>

]]></text>

</textData>