<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<textData 
	scrollColor="0x006699"
	trackColor="0x111111"
	bgdColor="0x000000">

<header><![CDATA[<font color = "#ffffff" size ="43">The Curse of the Glass Photo</font>]]></header>
<text><![CDATA[<img src="images/misc/curse1.jpg" width="185" height="185"/>
Our story opens in 1890 and transcends both period and modern day.  This old fashioned style ghost story combines horror elements with modern day twists and scare tactics. 
The movie targets one of the biggest market segments in the industry – teenagers and young adults – with potential crossover opportunities. 
Five students uncover a vengeful spirit that has lain dormant for over a century. Emotions and passions run high as our heroes battle to survive the supernatural.

The Actors who have been approached consist of both established names and up and coming actors. We believe that through a combination of the two this gives both a modern feel as well as a certain amount of gravitas to the feature. Thus opening the target audience up to both older and younger generations.

In Steve Bendelack we have an experienced and well respected director, who's ability to consistently deliver a commercially viable product is well documented. From his work on features such as "Mr. Bean's Holiday" Steve is able to take a story centered around a character with very little dialogue and produce a visually dramatic and interesting story, this requires extreme skill.

The script is a tightly written mystery thriller aiming to capture the imagination of its audience using stunning visuals and a solid story.  Combined with a supernatural style and embracing modern day scare tactics Trouble at Wolfe Hall is the exciting beginning of a new Thriller Franchise.
Steven Bendelack	-	Director
David Meadows		-	Cinematographer
Roxaneh Renton		-	Writer
Michael O'Sullivan	 -	Executive Producer	
Chris Bunyan 		-	Producer				
Graham Walker 		-	Music Supervisor
Kyz Kistell		-	Production Designer	
Robert Lever		-	Costume Designer

<img src="images/misc/curse2.jpg" width="390" height="260"/>
<br>]]></text>

</textData>
<!--<img src="images/misc/image2.jpg" width="264" height="264"/>-->