<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<textData 
	scrollColor="0x006699"
	trackColor="0x111111"
	bgdColor="0x000000">

<header><![CDATA[<font color = "#ffffff" size ="45">Basic Production Details</font>]]></header>

<text><![CDATA[<img src="images/misc/IMG_0815.JPG" width="224" height="184"/>
The Raven Club: Some call it, "Outcome Engineering", Winston Churchill called it "Corkscrew thinking", but at its core it's just simple manipulation!

The Raven Club: A slick and sophisticated feature film that is a cross between Fight Club and Dead Poets Society. It grabs your attention from the outset, keeping you on tenterhooks with surprising twists and turns, until a bombshell revelation in the final scene. 

Several narratives weave through the movie, similar to Lock Stock. The affluent look and feel of the feature will be comparable to Cruel Intentions and Dead Poets Society and it should acquire a superior cult status like that of Fight Club.
 
The Raven Club
Privately educated school boy, GILES, 18, has just lost his parents and only family in a double suicide. After the funeral, Giles and his best friend CHARLES, 18, head back to school where they meet up with their friends, CHRIS, JAMES and SIMON. Together, they are The Raven Club, a secret society that becomes embroiled in murder and manipulation after an accidental death, when a school boy prank goes horribly wrong. 
In the immediate aftermath of the accident, Giles makes constitutional changes to the Club, ostensibly to protect his friends from the police. Is Giles protecting his friends, or is there something much darker and more disturbing under his charming veneer? The cops are on their tails, but Giles always seems a few steps ahead, manipulating people and situations to meet his own ends.

The boys get mixed up with gangland London and even the Russian Mafia and when they enrol a new member into their club, MAY, 18, the stakes get even higher and the body count mounts. What unfolds is a dangerous, tangled web of double-crosses and seduction. Those that question Giles' intent discover death is the only alternative.

This small budget thriller has a Macro look and feel, with product placement from Noble Cars as well as several fashion houses. This feature will be filmed at some of the most luxurious and affluent locations in London.

Financials
The Enterprise Investment Scheme "EIS" is a government scheme that provides a range of tax reliefs for investors who subscribe for qualifying shares in qualifying companies. The investment is for three years and after the three years you can dispose of your shares with absolutely No Capital Gains Tax. 
The investment needs to be paid in full, as and when the shares are purchased. There is Loss Relief, where by, shares which can be disposed of at any time, qualify for such relief. 

A worst-case example from a £100,000 investment:
Income Tax Relief: once the investment is made, you will receive
30% of the investment             -- £30,000

Tax Rebate: if the production fails then the government will let you
rebate approximately 50% of the investment minus the initial 
Income Tax relief (£70,000)     -- £35,000				

So the downside is approximately 35% of the investment, in the 
case of this example, £35,000, i.e. the most the investor could lose 
is £35,000.
<!--<a href="http://s3.envato.com/files/1579205/template/index.html#/News" target="_blank"><font size="8" color="#006699">URL Link</font></a>-->

"If you are interested in learning more about The Raven Club click<a href="mailto:chris.bunyan@adamantinepictures.com"> HERE"</a>
 ]]></text>

</textData>